## **OBJECTIVE**

I aim to become a Web Developer with a reputable company that encourages teamwork, creativity, and continued learning where I have variety in my day. I have spent the last six years working in a tech store and look to convert my troubleshooting experience into skills beneficial in the development industry. I am seeking employment, where I am currently located, in Evansville, IN or would enjoy working remotely as well.

**EXPERIENCE** 

Solutions Specialist, Verizon Wireless

• Successfully implemented solutions for a wide array of cellular customers, creating personal connections to make tech look simple. Performed troubleshooting on iOS, android, Bluetooth and Wi-Fi electronics, as well as Verizon software

and POS submitting service tickets as required.

Provided training for new employees through hands-on experience and promoting a culture of continuous improvement.

Manager, Mark's Mattress Outlet and Fireworks.

2015 - 2016

Obtained new sales tactics and processes in or to generate maximum amount of sales to potential buyers.

Worked with Point of Sales, QuickBooks, and Microsoft Office applications.

Worked independently on most occasions while selling, pricing, ordering new inventory, and working with other managers to coordinate sales and product transfers across other Mark's locations.

**Inventory Specialist, Walmart Super-center** 

2014 - 2015

Documented inventory using electronic database. Aided management with product display.

Maximized customer service while managing time wisely to meet merchandise stocking deadlines.

Campus Recreation Assistant, USI 2012 - 2014 Security Personnel, Oakland City University 2010 - 2012

**EDUCATION** 

**CareerFoundry — Full-Stack Web Development Program** 

Immersive training program with emphasis on Full-Stack Web Development

University of Southern Indiana — Bachelor's of Science Individual Studies **Oakland City University — Criminal Justice** 

Shoals High School — Diploma

## **PROJECTS**

## **Portfolio Website**

A website designed to show potential employers the following projects. Written using HTML and CSS.

Pokédex

A small web application with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that loads data from an external API and enables the viewing of data points in detail.

**NixFlix-Server** 

Server side code is A RESTful API coded from scratch using Node.js.

**NixFlix-Client** 

A client-side frontend for your RESTful API, built with React.

**Meet-up App** 

A server-less, progressive web app that fetches data from the Google Calendar API.

 A JavaScript chat app built with React Native, featuring advanced functionality such as offline storage or geolocation.

Quiz App

A JavaScript guiz app built with Angular.

## **SKILLS**

- **HTML**
- CSS SCSS
- Bootstrap
- GitHub
- Git

- Javascript
- Express.JS
- Node.JS
- React
- AJAX iOuery

- **APIs**
- SOL
- Heroku
- Redux
- Angular
- MongoDB